Firewall Switch を正常に動作させるには、ユニバーサルアクセス環境設定の “補助装置を使用可能にする” にチェックを入れておく必要があります。ユニバーサルアクセス環境設定を開きますか？
キャンセル
OK
ウインドウ下部の “補助装置を使用可能にする” にチェックが入っていることをご確認ください。
For Firewall Switch to work, you must allow “osascript” to control your computer.
First click the “Privacy” tab at the top, then select “Accessibility” on the left. If necessary, click the lock button at the bottom to allow changes. Then make sure “osascript” is checked.