For Firewall Switch to work, you must check “enable access for assistive devices” in the Universal Access preference pane. Would you like to go there now?
Cancel
OK
Make sure the “enable access for assistive devices” option at the bottom is checked.
For Firewall Switch to work, you must allow Dashboard to control your computer.
First click the “Privacy” tab at the top of the System Preferences window. Select “Accessibility” on the left. If necessary, click the lock button at the bottom to allow changes. Then drag the Dashboard icon from the Finder into the list of apps on the right side of the System Preferences window.